AS YOU STOOD BY
EUN-SU AND HUI-SU
I thought he was working late?
What the hell?
Is everything okay?
You're home early.
Why am I flying to Shanghai... tomorrow?
What... what do you mean?
I have a one-way ticket to Shanghai,
in business class, tomorrow night.
- How come?
- I'm not sure. I wouldn't know.
I'm not asking you again. What did you do?
You're up to something, aren't you?
Eun-su came by to borrow an outfit.
What are you looking for?
Huh.
You're gonna have to explain this.
What are you up to?
- Huh?
- No!
Let her go!
You stay out of this. I warned you.
You stupid bitch.
Come on, come on.
- Hey!
- Ah!
Get up.
Now tell me why you're here.
Ah fuck!
Stop it! Stop it!
I'll ask you again. Why are you here, huh?
I told you to stay out of my business.
But you just had to cross the line. Huh?
So?
Were you planning
to kill me with this? Huh?
Choke me to death like this? Huh?
Like this? Huh?
Hey?
Didn't work.
'Cause I'm here to stay.
You hear?
I warned ya! Huh?
Now you pay with your life.
Die!
Hui-su. Hui-su, stop.
Eun-su, you need to go.
No one can know you were here.
- What? No.
- I was the one who did this!
No, we did this.
Eun-su!
This changes nothing.
I take Jang to the airport,
and he goes to Shanghai.
And then we drive out to the woods,
just like we said.
Pull it together.
Oh! You are here!
I hope it's not too forward,
but I brought you some tangerines.
I bought too many,
and they're all getting ripe,
so I thought I should share them.
Do you like tangerines?
Sorry, I'm not feeling well.
Do you mind leaving them by the door?
I think I might be contagious. Thank you.
SORRY, SCRATCHED YOUR CAR
PLEASE CONTACT ME, UNIT 1401
What if she heard the noise
and got suspicious?
She brought you fruit.
I know she knows what Jin-pyo was doing.
If she heard something,
then she probably came to check on you
and gave you her number just in case.
What if she came by to check on me
and realized what was going on?
- She could be calling the police.
- Mm, but she's never seen anything, right?
We stick to the plan, no matter what.
Were they at it again?
Today it was different.
I talked to her earlier,
and she had someone there.
You went up there?
To give her tangerines.
Let's go out!
I don't want to cook tonight.
- Seriously?
- I'm craving tteokbokki.
So I have to go change?
No, you don't. Those pants are clean.
Hyeon-ji! We're going out for dinner!
I'll clean it.
ALWAYS AND FOREVER
One, two, three...
♪ Friends walk through life together ♪
♪ Those happy days were mine ♪
What is this?
♪ One sentence, one lifetime ♪
♪ With heart and a cup of wine ♪
- You're leaving?
- Stay!
Shots when you get back!
It's my treat.
Feel free to order whatever you want.
Oh. I guess they knew that.
I don't think they have decent Korean
where you're going.
It came up pretty fast, huh?
Something wrong at home?
Uh...
Uh, I think my son needs me.
Oh.
So you miss him too much.
And your boat?
Hope you found a safe route?
Where do you start?
Pyeongtaek?
Gunsan?
Incheon?
Yeah.
Oh, they've been cracking down there.
You'll have to be careful.
Security is really tight.
You are heading to Incheon Harbor,
not airport?
The airport!
Yeah, but flying home would be great, huh?
If you're leaving 'cause of trouble,
I can't really cover for you.
Uh, you won't have to.
Jo Eun-su.
She knows you're leaving?
Jo Eun-su? Who's that?
We had a couple meetings at the warehouse.
I thought you met her.
Head back in. I'll be in soon.
Okay.
MR. JIN SO-BAEK
MR. JANG KANG
No way. He's no good.
All he does is sing the old songs
like the ones my grandma loved.
POWERING OFF
RESETTING DEVICE
Don't you remember
washing these last night?
I thought it'd be better to do it again.
I keep sneezing.
Did you spray all your perfume?
I wanted to hide the smell.
I guess I overdid it.
We already used air freshener last night.
You're more sensitive than me, I guess.
Did you get it ready?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah?
What, you're here?
I thought I'd show up early.
Good thinking.
Such a nice house.
And it smells really good.
Uh-huh.
So I asked you to come over
to try on this suit.
It looks good on you.
Thank you. It's a very nice suit.
And the bag too.
I'll give you the passport at the airport.
Is this all you have?
Yeah. I don't have much to bring back,
except what you bought.
You'll go down first.
The suitcase is heavy.
Oh, right.
I called a car for you.
Wait.
Here.
Oh!
Oh.
Ooh!
Wow.
I don't know what to say.
Thank you so much.
So I'll see you in a bit.
Yes.
First floor.
The doors are closing.
Right there.
Stop, I wanna get out.
I'll call you when he boards.
PARKING VIOLATION NOTICE
Where are the black ones?
Eun-su?
It's me.
Jin-young.
Sounds like you were expecting someone?
Uh, just one of my neighbors
who left her colander here.
Guess you're pretty close
with your neighbors,
greeting them in your bare feet and all.
Those aren't my brother's shoes, are they?
Uh, he only wears them
when he does volunteer work.
I'm not surprised.
I just need to freshen up.
My training was messy.
Hope you don't mind.
'Course not.
How'd this blood get here?
What's that smell?
Oh, I accidentally spilled
the air freshener.
Oh.
You wanna come sit in here?
I'm not staying.
My socks are clean.
Let me make you a coffee.
All right.
Is my brother at work?
Called him on the way here,
but it went straight to voicemail.
Is everything all right?
Yeah. It's a work thing.
Get me a glass of water instead,
would you?
Ow!
Oh, it's the snow globe.
Ah...
It's chipped right here.
I better get you that water.
Hey, didn't you have pictures
from your wedding or something over there?
Have you been arguing?
Here you are.
Get in.
NOH JIN-PYO
You must've found
a great investment opportunity, sir.
NOH JIN-PYO
Here's the combination
for the belt and suitcase.
BATTLE ROBOT
Jin-pyo,
the Presidential Office evaluation
is coming up soon.
You know they do
a family background check, right?
So I need you
to keep a low profile until I'm in.
DELETE MESSAGE
Shit.
He wouldn't have.
That snow globe's
heavy enough to kill her.
Especially when it comes
to your private life.
DELETE MESSAGE
Yeah?
It's just to remind you
to go to the foreigner's line
at Shanghai immigration.
Yes, of course.
Turn it on when you land,
then turn it off again before you toss it.
I will, yeah.
Farewell, Mr. Noh Jin-pyo.
Safe travels back to your boy.
- Is he gone?
- He just went through security.
Oh, Jin-pyo's sister sent a few texts
while I had his phone.
She was here a little earlier.
What? Why?
She saw the snow globe too.
Ah, well, don't worry about that.
The texts were about her evaluation.
But there was this other one
where she asked him to be more discreet.
Do you think maybe
he was hiding something?
I don't know.
Uh, please,
I'm waiting for a friend.
You and everyone else
who never actually move their car.
I can't go easy on nonresidents.
If I let it slide, there goes my job.
Yeah, yeah, it's just that
my friend's coming down. For real.
Which block is your friend in?
In two. Where I was.
It's my second one this week!
- Please! She's on her way!
- Ma'am! Please don't touch me.
- I'm sorry! Those tickets cost a fortune.
- Eun-su! Hi!
Goodness, Mrs. Jo! Please...
Hold on. I'll take that off!
Sorry. We're late for a show.
Have a good night!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I need to check something.
- All set.
- Mm.
Can't you go faster?
I don't wanna risk anything.
If we get in an accident,
we're totally screwed.
I just want this over with.
It's been harder than I thought.
You know, you keep doing that.
What?
It's like you're washing your hands.
Oh. They feel really sweaty.
Hey, this will be over soon.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, come on! Stop.
You know there's nothing
on your hands, Hui-su.
Right. I'll stop.
- Almost there...
- Oh, you gotta see this.
What's so funny?
It's so dumb, but I love it.
Dang. Spot's taken.
We'll have to go somewhere else.
I didn't know she had a visitor.
♪ Anything it takes... ♪
You have gone off route.
♪ I'm 'bout to break ♪
♪ Disposed on the way ♪
♪ 'Cause I ♪
♪ Can't do this ♪
♪ Alone ♪
♪ I tried ♪
♪ But I can't ♪
♪ Survive ♪
♪ This air ♪
♪ Unknown rhythm ♪
♪ Ringing in my ears ♪
♪ Tell me a poem ♪
♪ That could bring out my tears ♪
♪ 'Cause I ♪
♪ Can feel it ♪
♪ In my bones ♪
♪ The fear ♪
♪ And madness ♪
♪ That's filling up ♪
♪ This air ♪
I'll go get us something to drink.
Hi. You have a lot of stuff in here.
How much are those?
They're 5,000 each.
Oof! Pretty thirsty, weren't you?
I guess I was.
- Ah.
- Here you are.
Enjoy your meal.
- Thanks so much.
- Thanks a lot.
I don't have to skim the fat off, do I?
What, and lose the flavor?
Okay.
I'm starving.
Mmm!
This rice is amazing.
Gotta be locally grown. It's so good.
You're wolfing it down.
I can't help it.
I'm probably gonna ask for more rice.
Okay.
Hui-su.
- Uh...
- Want me to come in and hold your hair?
No, I'm fine.
Close the door?
I'd like to pay the bill, please.
Coming, yes!
Oh.
It's 25,000 altogether.
Uh, right.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
Can you go back to the apartment?
I don't really have a choice.
But I don't want to.
Did you sleep a little?
Mm-hmm.
Are you ready?
I guess so.
From now on, there'll be a lot
you'll need to face on your own.
I know.
But friendship means I'll always be there.
Better hope our friendship
doesn't land us in jail.
Time to turn our phones back on.
Right.
MISSED CALLS, MISSED MESSAGES
MR. JANG KANG
PUDONG, SHANGHAI
Looks like he got there safely.
Oh, thank God.
- Watch it.
- Ugh, wait.
- It's scratchy.
- I'll buy you good boots. Some sexy ones.
Those shoes...
- Oh! Did you twist your ankle?
- Crap.
Almost. It's a big soft spot.
Go around it.
Close one. Come on.
- What color boots do you want?
- Red. I know you like red.
MY SON
There was an accident
up the road.
We need to make way for the ambulances.
All the way to the side, please!
- It's okay.
- Yeah.
Medics are on the way?
There's blood on your car, ma'am.
- I hit something.
- You did?
It was, um, a small deer.
It ran out. I couldn't stop.
Just pop the trunk for a second, will ya?
No.
He can't!
Just wanna take a quick look, please.
I need you to open the trunk, ma'am.
Do you hear me?
♪ Anything it takes ♪
♪ I'm 'bout to break ♪
♪ Disposed on the way ♪
♪ 'Cause I ♪
♪ Can't do this ♪
♪ Alone ♪
♪ I tried ♪
♪ But I can't ♪
♪ Survive ♪
♪ This air ♪